Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Residential projects., 1939-1970
  - Subseries A: Apartments., 1945-1970.; 30 map folders.
    - (2 of 3)., 1947 (Folder 84)
      - Helen's Apartments., 1947.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 609. Helen's Apartments (Beck Apartments 11420-11430 Oxnard St.)
        11420-11430 Oxnard St. North Hollywood, CA.
        8 units.
      - Moss Construction Co. Apartments., 1947.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 610. Moss Construction Co. Apartments
        13th St. Manhattan Beach, CA.
        Owner: Moss Construction Company.
      - Beck Apartments., 1947.; 4.; 8 items.
        Job Number 628. Beck Apartments 11434 Oxnard St.
        11434 Oxnard St. North Hollywood, CA.
        3 units.
    - (3 of 3)., 1947 (Folder 85)
      - Dillaway Apartments., 1947.; 1.; 12 items.
        Job Number 637. Dillaway Apartments
        Corner of Woodman and Valleyheart Dr. Van Nuys, CA.
        10 units.
        Original drawings: surveyor's map, plans, elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. Don Dillaway.
      - Beck Apartments., 1947.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 639. Beck Apartments 11416 Oxnard St.
        11416 Oxnard St. North Hollywood, CA.
        4 units.
      - Smith Apartments., 1947.; 3.; 11 items.
        Job Number 650. Smith Apartments
        5746-5752 1/2 Camellia Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, exterior and interior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Ray Smith.
      - Kerns Apartment and Store Building., 1947.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 663. Kerns Apartment and Store Building
        11482 Oxnard St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R.E. Kerns.
    - (1 of 2)., 1948 (Folder 86)
      - "Harber Manor" Apartments., 1948.; 1.; 13 items.
        Job Number 658. "Harber Manor" Apartments, Arizona
        3300 Central Ave. Phoenix, Arizona.
        48 units.
        Owner: Guardian Development Company & Arizona Corporation.
      - Beck Apartments., 1948.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 676. Beck Apartments Simpson Ave.
        6336-40 1/2 Simpson Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
      - Deranian Apartments., 1948.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 687. Deranian Apartments
        Kester Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations, section, details.
        Owner: Mr. John Deranian.
      - The "Kesterton" Apartments., 1948.; 4.; 15 items.
        Job Number 690. The "Kesterton" Apartments
        4824 Kester Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        12 units.
        Original drawings: surveyor's map, plans, elevations, sections, details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Francis M. Boesch.
    - (2 of 2)., 1948 (Folder 87)
      - Smith Apartments., 1948.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 696. Smith Apartments
        Landale St. North Hollywood, CA.
        6 units.
        Owner: Bernice W. Smith.
      - Scallet Apartments., 1948.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 702. Scallet Apartments
        14519-21 benefit St. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, elevations, details.
        Owner: Mr. Edward A. Scallet.
      - The "Glennon Hardy" Apartments., 1948.; 3.; 14 items.
        Job Number 716. The "Glennon Hardy" Apartments
        4630-4634 Greenwood Pl & 2016 N. Vermont Ave. Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Charles Glennon Hardy & Yola O. Hardy.
      - Gies Apartments., 1948.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 732. Gies Apartments Addition
        12920 Moorpark St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section and elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. W. Geis.
    - (1 of 2)., 1949 (Folder 88)
      - Garden Terrace Apartments., 1949.; 1.; 18 items.
        Job Number 768. Garden Terrace Apartments (Moss McPike Apartments)
        Corner of Barbara Court & Dos Palos Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        18 units.
        Original drawings: surveyor's map, plans, sections, exterior and interior elevations, details, perspective.
        Owner: Edith R. Moss, Eugenie McPike, George McPike.
      - Wood Apartments., 1949.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 770. Wood Apartments
        10481-83 Eastborne Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H. Wood.
    - (2 of 2)., 1949 (Folder 89)
      - Bachelor Apartments., 1949.; 20 items.
        Job Number 776. Bachelor Apartments
        Lowry Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: Perspectives, surveyor's map, plans, sections, elevations, details.
        Owner: Gertrude Bachler.
    - (1 of 2)., 1950 (Folder 90)
      - "The Oaks" Apartments., 1950.; 1.; 16 items.
        Job Number 801. "The Oaks" Apartments
        Chapala St. Santa Barbara, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations, details, perspective.
        Owner: Camilla R. Tapie.
      - Lewis Apartments., 1950.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 802. Lewis Apartments
        951-955 North Vendome, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Alice F. Lewis.
      - Yanonali Gardens Apartments., 1950.; 3.; 11 items.
        Job Number 808. Yanonali Gardens Apartments
        Corner of Yanonali & Bath St. Santa Barbara, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, exterior and interior elevations, details.
        Owner: Yanonali Gardens Corporation.
    - (2 of 2)., 1950 (Folder 91)
      - Hollywood Gardens Apartments., 1950.; 1.; 24 items.
        Job Number 809. Hollywood Gardens Apartments
        6231-6239 Lexington Ave. Hollywood, CA.
        30 units.
        Owner: W.R. Faires & Cecil Lewis, Hollywood Gardens, Inc.
      - Corens Apartments., 1950.; 2.; 16 items.
        Job Number 810. Corens Apartments
        Montana Ave. & Sepulveda Terrace, West Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: surveyor's map, plans, exterior and interior elevations, perspective, details.
        Owner: Grace H., John F. & Barbara S. Corens.
      - Blake Apartments., 1950.; 3.; 2 items.
        Blake Apartments
        16th St. Manhattan Beach, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, exterior and interior elevations, section and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul J. Blake.
    - ., 1951-1952 (Folder 92)
      - D. & J. Bender Apartments., 1951.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 882. D. & J. Bender Apartments
        13561 1/2 Moorpark St. North Hollywood, CA.
      - 4 Unit Apartment Building., 1952.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 950. 4 Unit Apartment Building (originally marked Bender Apartments)
      - Murphy Apartments., 1952.; 3.; 5 items.
        Job Number 964. Murphy Apartments
        Via Lido Nord, Via Lido Soud, Newport Beach, CA.
        3 Units.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Elmo Murphy.
      - S. & J. Bender Apartments., 1952.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 965. S. & J. Bender Apartments
        Fulton Ave.
      - Slavin Apartments., 1952.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 978. Slavin Apartments
        Corner of Woolwine Dr. and Hazard Ave.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Leon Slavin.
    - ., 1954-1955 (Folder 93)
      - Harmon Apartments., 1954.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 54-36. Harmon Apartments
        Malibu, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Arthur Harmon.
      - Trietche Apartments., 1955.; 2.; 9 items.
        Job Number 55-18. Trietche Apartments
        Owner: Mr. Paul Trietsche.
      - Harrington Apartments., 1955.; 3.; 7 items.
        Job Number 55-39. Harrington Apartments
        Corner of Kester & Dickens, Los Angeles, CA.
        16 units.
        Owner: R. C. Harrington.
    - (1 of 2)., 1957 (Folder 94)
      - Boesch Apartments., 1957.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 57-1. Boesch Apartments
        6540 Sepulveda Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
      - Country Apartments., 1957.; 2.; 15 items.
        Job Number 57-7. Town & Country Apartments
        114 No. Fairway Lane, West Covina, CA.
        54 units.
        Owner: Hart- O'Hara- Kelso, Richard H. Hart.
    - (2 of 2)., 1957 (Folder 95)
      - Monello Apartments., 1957.; 19 items.
        Job Number 57-20. Monello Apartments
        20 units.
        Owner: F. Monello Company.
    - ., 1958 (Folder 96)
      - May Apartments., 1958.; 1.; 7 items.
        Job Number 58-21. May Apartments
        Barrington Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        Copy of engineer's drawings: plans, details, general notes.
        Owner: Mr. Ed May.
      - Madsen Apartments., 1958.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 58-11, 58-22. Madsen Apartments- South Commonwealth
        410 South Commonwealth.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations, perspective.
        Owner: J. R. Madsen.
      - Himelson Apartments., 1958.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 58-25. Himelson Apartments
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Himelson.
    - ., 1959 (Folder 97)
      - Erwin Apartments., 1959.; 15 items.
        Job Number 59-40. Erwin Apartments
        6267 Reseda Blvd. Reseda, CA.
        Original drawings and copies: plans, sections, exterior and interior elevations, details.
        Owner: Harry Bassett.
    - ., 1960 (Folder 98)
      - Starlite Apartments., 1960.; 29 items.
        Job Number 60-31. Starlite Apartments
        6819 Hinds Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        29 Units.
        Owner: Doosie B. Haas, Builder.
    - (1 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 99)
      - Madsen Apartments., 1961.; 27 items.
        Job Number 61-7. Madsen Apartments- South Alexandria
        522 South Alexandria Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        12 Units.
        Owner: Madsen Company.
    - (2 of 2)., 1961 (Folder 100)
      - Madsen Apartments., 1961.; 1.; 13 items.
        Job Number 61-26. Madsen Apartments- South Alexandria
        9 Units.
        Set of original drawings: architectural and electrical.
      - Madsen Apartment., 1961.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 61-45? Madsen Apartment- East Ocean
        East Ocean Blvd. Long Beach, CA.
        8-11 Units.
        Preliminary drawings: plans.
      - Ross Apartments., 1961.; 3.; 8 items.
        Job Number 61-45. Ross Apartments
        5440 East Ocean Blvd. Long Beach, CA.
        Owner: A.B & B.C Ross.
    - ., 1962 (Folder 101)
      - MacInnis Apartments., 1962.; 1.; 29 items.
        Job Number 62-3. MacInnis Apartments
        Langdon Ave. Sepulveda, CA.
        44 units.
        Original drawings and revision drawings: plans, sections, elevations, details.
        Owner: MacInnis Construction Company.
      - Lipps Apartments., 1962.; 2.; 7 items.
        Job Number 62-16. Lipps Apartments
        4917 Whitsett Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. Wilberta Lipps.
    - (1 of 2)., 1963 (Folder 102)
      - Dalton Apartments., 1963.; 1.; 2 items.
        Dalton Apartments
        5224 Yarmouth, Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, interior and exterior elevations, details.
        Owner: John R. Dalton.
      - Moyer Apartments., 1963.; 2.; 16 items.
        Job Number 63-24, 64-26. Moyer Apartments
        Ellice St. West Malibu, CA.
        Original drawings and copies: plans, sections, elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Moyer.
    - (2 of 2)., 1963 (Folder 103)
      - Pedrotta Apartments., 1963.; 25 items.
        Job Number 63-29. Pedrotta Apartments
        5020 Tujunga Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        39 units.
        Owner: Mr. Chas. Pedrotta.
    - (Rancho Malibu Miguel--1 and 2 of 3)., 1964 (Box 104, Box 105)
      - Rancho Malibu Miguel, Rancho Malibu Miguel West, Rancho Malibu Miguel Reef., 1964-1967.; ca. 100 items.
        Job Numbers 64-1, 64-28, 66-22, 67-1. Rancho Malibu Miguel, Rancho Malibu Miguel West, Rancho Malibu Miguel Reef
        Pacific Coast Highway, Malibu, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Harvey Knox.
    - (Rancho Malibu Miguel--3 of 3)., 1964 (Folder 106)
      - Rancho Malibu Miguel, Rancho Malibu Miguel West, Rancho Malibu Miguel Reef., 1964-1967.; ca. 50 items.
        Original drawings: Plumbing, electrical layouts and details.
        Photos and magazine cutouts.
    - ., 1968 (Folder 107)
      - Spoon Apartments., 1968.; ca. 20 items.
        Job Number 68-16. Spoon Apartments
        9255 Doheney Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        37-40 units.
        Owner: I.J. Spoon.
    - ., 1969 (Folder 108)
      - Tatco Apartments., 1969.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 69-15. Tatco Apartments
        2508 W. Grand Ave. Alhambra, CA.
        Copy of engineer's drawings.
        Owner: Tatco Development.
      - Stanwald Apartments., 1969.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 69-16. Stanwald Apartments
        604 Fremont Ave. South Pasadena, CA.
        Owner: Stanwald Building Co.
    - ., 1970 (Folder 109)
      - Hancock Park Terrace Apartments., 1970.; ca. 30 items.
        Job Number 70-8. Hancock Park Terrace Apartments
        Corner of Wilcox and Melrose Ave. Los Angeles, CA.
        66-70 units.
        Owner: Ray Rosendahl.
  - Subseries B: Private homes., 1939-1970.; 73 map folders
    Homes for private clients, as opposed to developers, predominantly in the San Fernando Valley.
    - Miscellaneous--sketches. (Folder 110)
      - Perspectives., no date.; ca. 25 items.
        Perspectives
        Original and copies of perspectives on trace and paper for residences, including Banker, Le Baron, Dewing reading room, Root, Boyle BBQ, Goble kitchen, Driver, Erdy and guest house prototype.
    - Miscellaneous. (Folder 111)
      - Fields residence., no date.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 4091? Fields residence
        San Ysidro Drive, Los Angeles, CA. Original drawings and copies: plans, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. Herbert Fields.
      - Avent residence., no date.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 4302. Avent residence
        4101 Beck Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Copy of drawings under the name of C.W. Kern paper: plans, details, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: John Avent.
      - Ayres & Fiege residence., no date.; 3.; 1 item.
      - Jones residence., no date.; 4.; 1 item.
        Jones residence
        Original drawing: plans, section, elevations and details.
        Owner: Robert E. Jones.
      - Lawson residence., no date.; 5.; 2 items.
        Original drawings: plans and elevations.
      - Zolla residence., no date.; 6.; 3 items.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations.
    - ., 1939-1941 (Folder 112)
      - Wilson residence., 1939.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 201. Wilson residence
        1403 Parkway, Beverly Hills, CA.
        Original drawings and copies: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Mrs. Edith E. Wilson.
      - Lippus residence., 1941.; 2.; 3 items.
        Lippus residence
        Peach Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawings: interior and exterior elevations, details and plans.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Edward Lippus.
    - (1 of 5)., 1946 (Folder 113)
      - Theodore residence., 1946.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 461. Theodore residence
        15058 Reyneta Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations and details.
        Owner: Paul & Jaunita Theodore.
      - Baldwin residence., 1946.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 467. Baldwin residence
        Woodley Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Earl Baldwin.
      - Vogt residence., 1946.; 3.; 9 items.
        Job Number 468. Vogt residence
        6221 Fallbrook Ave. Canoga Park, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. A.G. Vogt.
    - (2 of 5)., 1946 (Folder 114)
      - Chotiner residence., 1946.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 479. Chotiner residence
        S.E. Corner of Sherman Oaks Circle and Warden, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Willard Chotiner.
      - Tomilson residence., 1946.; 2.; 10 items.
        Job Number 501. Tomilson residence
        3311 Oakville Rd. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E.Tomilson.
    - (3 of 5)., 1946 (Folder 115)
      - Stuart residence., 1946?; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 502. Stuart residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Virgil Stuart.
      - Lane residence., 1946.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 504. Lane residence
        5058 Van Alden Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Lane.
      - Defore residence., 1946.; 3.; 9 items.
        Job Number 509. Defore residence
        Mandeville Canyon and Westridge Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections, details, perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Don Defore.
      - Poss residence., 1946.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 511. Poss residence
        4033 Woodcliff Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John R. Poss, Jr.
    - (4 of 5)., 1946 (Folder 116)
      - Lawlor residence., 1946.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 512. Lawlor residence
        Magnesia Falls Dr. Rancho Mirage, Palm Springs, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, interior and exterior elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John Lawlor.
      - Clay residence., 1946.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 515. Clay residence
        23119 Sylvan St. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Albert Clay.
      - Gordon residence., 1946.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 516. Gordon residence
        4907 Norwich Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Sam Gordon.
      - Zabel residence., 1946.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 518. Zabel residence
        Buena Park Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Henry Zabel.
    - (5 of 5)., 1946 (Folder 117)
      - Balog residence., 1946.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 519. Balog residence
        13044 Greenleaf St. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, exterior and interior elevations and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. P. J. Balog.
      - Scarpitta residence., 1946.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 520. Scarpitta residence
        Burbank Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Guy Scarpitta.
      - Spitzer residence., 1946.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 539, 540. Spitzer residence
        1321 Valley Heart Dr. Burbank, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, details, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. Ned H. Spitzer Jr.
      - Stoddard residence., 1946.; 4.; 7 items.
        Job Number 542. Stoddard residence
        4550 Gloria Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections, details and perspective.
        Includes elevation of Caruso residence.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. L. Stoddard.
      - Bixby residence., 1946.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 548. Bixby residence
        Martha St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. F. Bixby.
      - Murphy residence., 1946.; 6.; 4 items.
        Job Number 603. Murphy residence
        Owner: Paul Murphy.
    - (1 of 4)., 1947 (Folder 118)
      - Caruso residence., 1947-1948.; 1.; 17 items.
        Job Numbers 606, 606A, 606B. Caruso residence
        Big Oak Dr. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations and section and details.
        Specifications. Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Caruso.
      - Gault residence., 1947.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 613. Gault residence
        Glenoaks Blvd. Sunland, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Claude Gault.
      - Tennis residence., 1947.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 614. Tennis residence
        Original drawings: plans, elevations and section.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. G. Ed. Tennis.
      - Fiege residence., 1947.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 616. Hart & Fiege residence
        5917 Nagle Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. H. Hart & H. Feige.
    - (2 of 4)., 1947 (Folder 119)
      - Edwards residence., 1947.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 617. Edwards residence
        Nardian Way, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. W. Edwards.
      - Jameson residence., 1947.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 632. Jameson residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. K.K.Jameson.
      - Hickman residence., 1947.; 3.; 12 items.
        Job Number 633. Hickman residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. P. Hickman.
    - (3 of 4)., 1947 (Folder 120)
      - Holson residence., 1947.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 641. Holson residence
        4018 Mary Ellen St. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Dwight Holson.
      - Curlett residence., 1947.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 642. Curlett residence
        Del Gado St. Sherman Woods, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations and sections and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John Curlett.
      - Culver Desert Dwelling., 1947.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 644. Culver Desert Dwelling
        Rancho Mirage, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Dave Culver.
      - Adams residence., 1947.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 648. Adams residence
        4464 Matilija Ave.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. A. E. Adams.
    - (4 of 4)., 1947 (Folder 121)
      - Fisher residence., 1947.; 1.; 16 items.
        Job Number 651. Fisher residence
        Ninth St. Marshalltown, Iowa.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. W. Fisher.
      - Bloomfield residence., 1947.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 653. Bloomfield residence
        Bagley St. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. B. Bloomfield.
      - Claiborne residence., 1947.; 4.; 5 items.
        Job Number 662. Claiborne residence
        18801 Wells Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harry C. Claiborne.
      - Watland residence., 1947.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 666. Watland residence
        12624 Moorpark St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mrs. Rose Watland.
      - Bender residence., 1947.; 6.; 4 items.
        Job Number 667, 669. Bender residence
        4225 Mammoth Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. Dave Bender.
    - (1 of 5)., 1948 (Folder 122)
      - Pomeroy residence., 1948.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 522. Pomeroy residence
        Louise Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Edna Pomeroy.
      - Graham residence., 1948.; 2.; 4 items.
        Graham residence
        Encino Dr. Granada Hills, Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Floyd Graham.
      - Rolston residence., 1948.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 664. Rolston residence
        Woodvale Rd. Sherman Woods, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Paul Rolston.
      - Culver Duplex., 1948.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 677. Culver Duplex
      - Palermo residence., 1948.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 678. Palermo residence
        12841 Landale St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: G. Palermo.
    - (2 of 5)., 1948 (Folder 123)
      - Daggs residence., 1948.; 1.; 7 items.
        Job Number 684. Daggs residence
        Woodvale Rd. Sherman Woods (Encino), CA.
        Owner: Willis H. & Sunshine K. Daggs.
      - Steinman residence., 1948.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 685. Steinman residence
        13515 Foothill Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. C. Steinman.
      - Lane residence., 1948.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 686. Lane residence
        Chaplin Ave. Encino, CA.
      - Bollinger-Bailliff., 1948.; 4.; 10 items.
        Job Number 688. Bollinger-Bailliff two family residence
        2903 Waverly Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R.W. Bollinger and J. May Bailiff.
    - (3 of 5)., 1948 (Folder 124)
      - Feld residence., 1948.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 689. Feld residence
        11627 Sunshine Terrace, Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mary B. & Irving Feld.
      - Suerken residence., 1948.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 691. Suerken residence
        13040 Moorpark Dr. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Suerken.
      - Button Desert residence., 1948.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 698. Button Desert residence
        Owner: Mr. Ronald Button.
      - Kane residence., 1948.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 703. Kane residence
        14727 Valley Vista Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Kane.